Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. Samuel Taylor Coleridge miscellaneous correspondence (MS Eng 947): Guide.
Samuel Taylor Coleridge miscellaneous correspondence,
1794-1833.
Houghton Library, Harvard College Library, Harvard University
MS Eng 947
Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834.
1 volume (.16 linear ft.)
Letters by the English poet Samuel Taylor Coleridge to various correspondents.
Received from various sources at various times.
There are no restrictions on physical access to this material.
Coleridge was an English poet.
Arranged alphabetically by correspondent.
Letters from Coleridge to various correspondents including Joseph Cottle, Frederic Mansel Reynolds, and Charles Augustus Tulk.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to William Taylor; [n.p.], 25 Jan 1800., 1s.(4p.).
  Concerns Gottfried August Bürger.
  *74M-12. Purchased with the Perkins fund, 13 November 1974.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [ ]; [n.p.] 19 Mar 1819., 1s.(1p.)
  Recat. fr. 194578.5 (26).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [Mrs. ] Aders; [n.p.] 3 Jun 1824., 1s.(3p.)
  Recat. fr. MS Eng 778.5.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [Mrs. ] Aders; Highgate, 6 Feb. 1826., 1s.(1p.)
  *48M-256. Purchased from Raphael King, Ltd., 17 June 1949.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Thomas Allsop; Highgate, 21 Sep 1820., 2s.(3p.)
  *48M-257. Purchased from Raphael King, Ltd., 17 June 1949.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Thomas Allsop; [n.p.] 12 Feb 1822., 1s.(4p.)
  Recat. fr. 194578.5 (31).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [Joseph] Cottle; [n.p., ca. 1 Apr 1706], 1s.(2p.)
  Recat. fr. 194578.5 (17).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [Joseph] Cottle; [Crewekern, 1797], 1s.(3p.)
  Recat. fr. 9478.5 (15).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [Joseph] Cottle; [Stowey, 3 Jul 1797], 1s.(4p.)
  Includes errata list.
  Recat. fr. 194578.5 (16).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [Joseph] Cottle; [Stowey, ca.20 Nov 1797], 1s.(4p.)
  Top half of f.1 lacking.
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (18).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Joseph Cottle; [n.p., 1814], 1s.(2p.)
  *48M-258. Gift of Merle Mercer, 17 June 1949.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Joseph Cottle; [n.p., 1814], 1s.(4p.)
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [William] Ayrton; Highgate, [26 Jan 1818], 1s.(3p.)
  Recat. fr. 194578.5 (11).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [Miss ] [B]; [n.p.] 17 Apr 1819., 1s.(2p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (27).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [Mrs.] Bates; Highgate 28 or 29 Nov 1828., 1s.(2p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (35).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [ ] Boosey, Jr.; [n.p.] 20 May 1817., 1s.(4p.)
  1915. Gift of Robert Gould Shaw.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [John] Colson; [n.p.] 8 Dec 1796., 1s.(2p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (14).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [Miss ] Cruikshank; [n.p., 21] Sep 1807., 1s.(2p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (20).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to George Dyer; [Bristol, 29 May 1796], 1s.(2p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (3).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to John Fellowes; Tewkesbury, 28 Jul 1796., 1s.(3p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (13).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [John Hookham] Frere; Highgate, 2 Jul 1816., 1s.(3p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (23).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [G] Frere: Highgate [19 Dec 1816], 1s.(3p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (25).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to James Gillman; Porta Arietina, 31 Oct 1821., 1s.(4p.)
  *47M-2F. Purchased from Raphael King, 8 July 1947.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to James Gillman; [Ramsgate, 11 Nov 1822], 1s.(4p.)
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to James Gillman; [Ramsgate, 25 Oct 1824], 1s.(4p.)
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to James Gillman; [N.P., late Oct 1825], 1s.(4p.)
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to James Gillman; [Windsor, 24 Oct 1825], 1s.(4p.)
  *47M-2F1. Purchased from Raphael King, 8 July 1947.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to James Gillman; [Ramsgate, 23 Nov 1825., 1s.(4p.)
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to James [Gillman Jr.]; [n.p., n.d.], 1s.(2p.)
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [John Mathew] Gutch; Highgate, 7 Aug 1816., 1s.(4p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (24).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [James Augustus] Hessey; [n.p., ca. 10 Dec 1823], 1s.(4p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (7).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [James Auhustus] Hessey; [n.p., ca. 1 Feb 1824], 1s.(3p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (6).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [James Augustus] Hessey; Highgate [16 Feb 1825], 1s.(2p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (32).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [James Augustus] Hessey; [Highgate, 7 May 1825], 1s.(2p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (33).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1934. A.L.s. to Thomas Hurst; [n.p., ca. 1830], 1s.(4p.)
  *42M-1039F. Purchased from Goodspeed's Book Shop, July 1943.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Basil Montagu; Grasmere, [12 Jan 1809], 1s.(4p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (21).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to John J. Morgan; [n.p., 14 Jul 1814], 1s.(4p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (22).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to John J. Morgan; Highgate, 28 Jan 1818., 2s.(3p.)
  Recat. fr. the Autograph file.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [ ] Neumagen; [n.p., n.d.], 1s.(4p.)
  Formerly inserted in C's copy of Walker's Rhyming dictionary.
  Removed from 19478.620*
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [Thomas Phillips]; [n.p.] 8 Jun 1818., 1s.(1p.)
  *48M-20. Purchased from Myers and Co., 1 Jul 1948.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Frederic Mansel Reynolds; Highgate, 12 May 1825., 2s.(2p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (34).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Frederic Mansel Reynolds; [Highgate, 3 Aug 1828?], 2s.(7p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (8).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [Frederick Mansel Reynolds] [n.p., 25 Aug 1828], 1s.(4p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (2).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [Frederic Mansel Reynolds]; [n.p., ca. 30 Jul 1829], 1s.(4p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (9).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Richard Brinsley Sheridan; Stowey, 6 Feb 1797., 1s.(3p.)
  *45M-218F. Purchased from Quaritch, 24 Dec 1945.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Robert Southey; [n.p., 3 Nov 1796], 1s.(2p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (1).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Taylor and Hessey; Highgate [23 Apr 1819], 1s.(3p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (28).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to John Tobin; Keswick, 17 Sep 1800., 1s.(4p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (19).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Charles Augustus Tulk; Highgate [24 Nov 1818], 1s.(3p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (4).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Charles Augustus Tulk; Highgate, 20 Jan 1820., 1s.(4p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (30).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Charles Augustus Tulk; [Highgate, 1825], 1s.(4p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (5).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to J.B.Williams; [n.p.] 13 Feb 1827., 1s.(3p.)
  Recat. fr. x27.84.5.
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to [William Taylor] Worship; Highgate, 12 May 1819., 2s.(3p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (29).
- Coleridge, Samuel Taylor, 1772-1834. A.L.s. to Francis Wrangham; [n.p.] 24 Oct 1794., 1s.(4p.)
  Recat. fr. 19478.5 (12).